Preliminary Inventory of the Yearbook on International Communist Affairs Collection, 1966-1991
Hoover Institution Archives
Yearbook on International Communist Affairs Collection,
1966-1991
Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace
180 cubic ft. boxes, 256 ms. boxes, 30 card file boxes
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Clippings, serial issues, other printed matter, and notes, relating to the activities of communist parties throughout the world, 1966-1983. Used as research material for the Yearbook on International Communist Affairs published annually by the Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection open for research.
Access Points
Communism.; Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace.; Yearbook on international communist affairs.
Container List
- Asia (Box 1)
  - General, 1966
  - Cambodia - India, 1966 (Box 2)
  - Indonesia - Nepal, 1967 (Box 3)
  - New Zealand - Vietnam, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Asia General - Japan, 1968 (Box 5)
  - Japan - North Vietnam, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Thailand - China, 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - China - Laos, 1969 (Box 8)
  - Laos - North Vietnam, 1969 (Box 9)
  - South Vietnam - China, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - China - Philippines, 1970 (Box 11)
  - Taiwan - China, 1970 (Box 12)
  - China - Pakistan, 1970-1971 (Box 13)
  - Philippines - South Korea, 1971-1972 (Box 14)
  - South Vietnam - Korea, 1972-1973 (Box 15)
  - North Korea - North Vietnam, 1973 (Box 16)
  - South Vietnam, 1973 (Box 17)
- Eastern Europe and Soviet Union (Box 18)
  - Eastern Europe General - Romania, 1966
  - Romania - Bulgaria, 1967 (Box 19)
  - Bulgaria - Romania, 1967 (Box 20)
  - Soviet Union, 1967 (Box 21)
  - European Security - Warsaw Pact, 1967-1968 (Box 22)
  - Budapest - Hungary, 1968 (Box 23)
  - Poland - Soviet Union, 1968 (Box 24)
  - Soviet Union - Conference Committee Parties, 1968-1969 (Box 25)
  - Soviet Union - Czechoslovakia, 1969 (Box 26)
  - Czechoslovakia - East Germany, 1969 (Box 27)
  - Warsaw Pact - Hungary, 1969 (Box 28)
  - Hungary - Romania, 1969 (Box 29)
  - Romania - Soviet Union, 1969 (Box 30)
  - Soviet Union - Yugoslavia, 1969 (Box 31)
  - Yugoslavia - Bulgaria, 1969-1970 (Box 32)
  - Bulgaria - East Germany, 1970 (Box 33)
  - East Germany - Hungary, 1970 (Box 34)
  - Hungary - Romania, 1970 (Box 35)
  - Romania - U.S.S.R., 1970 (Box 36)
  - U.S.S.R. - CMEA, 1970 (Box 37)
  - CMEA - Bulgaria, 1971 (Box 38)
  - Bulgaria - Czechoslovakia, 1971 (Box 39)
  - East Germany - Hungary, 1971 (Box 40)
  - Poland, 1971 (Box 41)
  - Poland - Romania, 1971 (Box 42)
  - U.S.S.R., 1971 (Box 43)
  - U.S.S.R. - Yugoslavia, 1971 (Box 44)
  - Yugoslavia - Czechoslovakia, 1971 (Box 45)
  - Czechoslovakia - East Germany, 1972 (Box 46)
  - Hungary - Poland, 1972 (Box 47)
  - Poland - U.S.S.R., 1972 (Box 48)
  - U.S.S.R. - Eastern Europe, 1972-1973 (Box 49)
  - East-West Europe - Czechoslovakia, 1973 (Box 50)
  - Czechoslovakia - Poland, 1973 (Box 51)
  - Poland - U.S.S.R., 1973 (Box 52)
  - U.S.S.R., 1973 (Box 53)
  - U.S.S.R. - Yugoslavia, 1973 (Box 54)
- Middle East and Africa (Box 55)
  - West Africa - Jordan, 1966-1967
  - Kuwait - Algeria, 1967-1969 (Box 56)
  - Angola - Egypt, 1969-1970 (Box 57)
  - Middle East - Israel, 1970-1971 (Box 58)
  - Israel - Zimbabwe, 1971-1973 (Box 59)
- Western Europe (Box 60)
  - Austria - Cyprus, 1966-1967
  - Denmark - Great Britain, 1967 (Box 61)
  - Greece - Turkey, 1967 (Box 62)
  - Western Europe - France, 1968 (Box 63)
  - West Germany - Spain, 1968 (Box 64)
  - Sweden - France, 1968-1969 (Box 65)
  - West Germany - Turkey, 1969 (Box 66)
  - Western European General - West Germany, 1970 (Box 67)
  - West Germany - Austria, 1970-1971 (Box 68)
  - Belgium - Holland, 1971 (Box 69)
  - Iceland - West Germany, 1971-1972 (Box 70)
  - West Germany - Switzerland (Box 71)
- Western Hemisphere (Box 72)
  - Bolivia, 1966-1967
  - Chile - Paraguay, 1967-1968 (Box 73)
  - El Salvador - Guadalupe, 1968 (Box 74)
  - Guatemala - Argentina, 1968-1969 (Box 75)
  - Argentina - Cuba, 1969 (Box 76)
  - Cuba - Uruguay, 1969 (Box 77)
  - Uruguay - Chile, 1969-1970 (Box 78)
  - Chile - Haiti, 1970 (Box 79)
  - Honduras - Chile, 1970-1971 (Box 80)
  - Ecuador - PSCG, 1971 (Box 81)
  - Columbia - Cuba, 1971 (Box 82)
  - El Salvador - Venezuela, 1971 (Box 83)
  - Antigua - Cuba, 1972 (Box 84)
  - Cuba - Bolivia, 1972-1973 (Box 85)
  - Brazil - Cuba, 1973 (Box 86)
  - Curacao - Venezuela, 1973 (Box 87)
- 1974 (Box 88)
  - Cambodia - Costa Rica, 1974
  - Cuba - I.O.J., 1974 (Box 89)
  - WFTU - Brazil, 1974 (Box 90)
  - Brazil - Czechoslovakia, 1974 (Box 91)
  - Denmark - East Germany, 1974 (Box 92)
  - West Germany - Laos, 1974 (Box 93)
  - ? - Panama, 1974 (Box 94)
  - Peru - Spain, 1974 (Box 95)
  - Sri Lanka - North Vietnam, 1974 (Box 96)
- 1975 (Box 97)
  - North Vietnam - Zanzibar - Zambia, 1975
- 1976 (Box 98)
  - Summary of 1976 - Bulgaria, 1976
  - Burma - U.S.S.R., 1976 (Box 99)
  - Congo - Ecuador, 1976 (Box 100)
  - Egypt - Hong Kong, 1976 (Box 101)
  - Hungary - Pakistan, 1976 (Box 102)
  - ? - Portugal, 1976 (Box 103)
  - Portugal - U.S. Latin America, 1976 (Box 104)
  - U.S.S.R., 1976 (Box 105)
- 1975 (Box 106)
  - NYT - Arab Guerillas, 1975
  - Arabian Peninsula - Columbia, 1975 (Box 107)
  - Chile - Cyprus, 1975 (Box 108)
  - Czechoslovakia - Great Britain, 1975 (Box 109)
  - Greece - Laos, 1975 (Box 110)
  - Latin America - Peru, 1975 (Box 111)
  - Philippines - Portugal, 1975 (Box 112)
  - Portugal - Spain, 1975 (Box 113)
  - Sri Lanka - Venezuela, 1975 (Box 114)
  - North Vietnam - Summary of 1977, 1975, 1977 (Box 115)
- 1977 (Box 116)
  - AALAPSO - China, 1977
  - China - East Germany, 1977 (Box 117)
  - Ghana - New Zealand, 1977 (Box 118)
  - Nicaragua - Spain, 1977 (Box 119)
  - Spanish Sahara - Zanzibar, 1977 (Box 120)
- 1978 (Box 121)
  - AALAPSO - China, 1978
  - China - Ecuador, 1978 (Box 122)
  - El Salvador - Hungary, 1978 (Box 123)
  - India - South Korea, 1978 (Box 124)
  - Latin America - Romania, 1978 (Box 125)
  - San (Box 126)
  - Vietnam, 1978 (Box 127)
  - China, 1978 (Box 128)
- 1979 (Box 129)
  - NYT - Burma, 1979
  - Canada - Greece, 1979 (Box 130)
  - Granada - Laos, 1979 (Box 131)
  - Latin America - Spain, 1979 (Box 132)
  - Jordan - Zanzibar, 1979 (Box 133)
- 1980 (Box 134)
  - Summary of 1980 - Cuba, 1980
  - Cuba - West Germany, 1980 (Box 135)
  - Ghana - Laos, 1980 (Box 136)
  - Latin America - Poland, 1980 (Box 137)
  - Portugal - China, 1980 (Box 138)
  - China, 1980 (Box 139)
- AAJA - World Youth Festival (International Communist Frontal Organization) (Box 140)
- Afro-Asian Summit - NYT review (Box 141)
- NYT summary - international affairs (Box 142)
- Unidentified (Box 143-196)
- Africa (Box 197-198)
- America (Box 199-200)
- Eastern Europe and USSR (Box 200-201)
- "Asia General" folder and China (Box 201-203)
- Japan, Indonesia, and Korea (Box 203)
- Laos, Malaysia, Philippines, Singapore, and Sri Lanka (Box 204)
- Poland, 1977-1979 (3 folders)
- Yugoslavia, 1978-1979
- GDR, 1977-1979
- Western Europe (Box 205)
- Eastern Europe - USSR, 1977-1981 (Box 206)
- Yearbook 1981 (Box 207)
  - Miscellaneous - El Salvador
  - Ethiopia - Kampuchea (Box 208)
  - Kampuchea - Poland (Box 209)
  - Poland - Zimbabwe (Box 210)
- Albania, 1980-1981 (Box 211)
- Bulgaria, 1981-1982 (Box 211-212)
- Czechoslovakia, 1981 (Box 212)
- GDR, 1981
- Hungary, 1981
- Poland, 1980-1983 (Box 213-218)
- Romania, 1981-1983 (Box 218-220)
- 1983 (Box 221-227)
  - Asia and the Pacific, including Japan
  - Non-aligned countries and Eastern Europe (Box 227-229)
  - USSR (Box 230-231)
  - Middle East and Africa (Box 232-235)
  - Americas (Box 236-241)
  - Western Europe (Box 241-242)
  - Introduction (Box 243)
- 1984 (Box 244-249)
  - Americas
  - Western Europe (Box 249-251)
  - Asia (Box 252-258)
  - Eastern Europe (Box 258-264)
  - Africa (Box 265-267)
  - Introduction (Box 268)
- 1985 (Box 269-270)
  - Introduction
  - Asia and the Pacific (Box 271-274)
  - USSR (Box 274-276)
  - Eastern Europe (Box 276-281)
  - Africa and the Middle East (Box 281-285)
  - Americas (Box 285-290)
  - Western Europe (Box 290-295)
- 1986 (Box 296-297)
  - Introduction
  - Americas (Box 298-303)
  - Western Europe (Box 304-306)
  - Asia and Pacific (Box 306-311)
  - USSR (Box 211-314)
  - Eastern Europe (Box 315-320)
  - Africa and the Middle East (Box 320-324)
- 1976-1987 (Box 325-328)
  - Poland, 1986
  - Yugoslavia, 1986 (Box 328-330)
  - Introduction, 1987 (Box 330-331)
  - Americas, 1987 (Box 331-336)
  - Western Europe, 1987 (Box 336-340)
  - Eastern Europe, 1987 (Box 341-349)
  - USSR, 1987 (Box 349-352)
  - Asia and Pacific, 1987 (Box 353-359)
  - Africa and the Middle East, 1987 (Box 359-364)
  - Guyana, 1976-1984 (Box 365-367)
- 1988 (Box 368)
  - Introduction
  - Americas (Box 368-371)
  - Western Europe (Box 372-373)
  - Asia and Pacific (Box 374-382)
  - USSR (Box 382-388)
  - Eastern Europe (Box 388-393)
  - Africa and the Middle East (Box 394-397)
- 1990 (Box 398)
  - Introduction and Americas
  - Americas (Box 398-402)
  - Western Europe (Box 402-404)
  - Eastern Europe (Box 404-407)
  - USSR (Box 407-413)
  - China (Box 413-415)
  - Asia and Pacific (Box 514-419)
  - Middle East (Box 419-421)
  - Africa (Box 421-422)
- 1988-1991 (Box 423-425)
  - Africa (1990-1991)
  - Middle East (1990-1991) (Box 426-428)
  - Asia and Pacific (1990-1991) (Box 429-437)
  - Western Europe (1990-1991) (Box 438-451)
  - Eastern Europe (1990-1991) (Box 451-454)
  - Americas (1990-1991) (Box 455-459)
  - Poland (1988-1989) (Box 460-463)
- 1991 (Box 464-465)
  - Romania (1990)
  - USSR (1991) (Box 465-466)